# E L I S H A L E E

# UI/UX Associate Manager

## SUMMARY

Experienced UI/UX manager with over 10 years of experience in many different major companies, such as LG, Hyundai Motor, Pantech, Korean Air, Hanjin USA, and Forever 21. Highly self-motivated professional with proven ability to identify, analyze, and solve problems effectively.

# EXPERIENCE

#### Forever 21 – UI/UX Associate Manager

Los Angeles, CA | 07.2014 ~ Present

Involved in a lot of complex projects to meet the company's business goal. Recently revamped Forever 21's US Website to RWD (Responsive Design) according to my proposal. Researched pros and cons, analyzed competitors, and created new business strategy to convince executive team. After implementation, the company's sales revenue, UPT, traffic, and conversion rate have increased. Most importantly, mobile conversion rate skyrocketed from average 1.03 to 1.98.

- Provide vision, direction, and lead UI/UX team.
- Define design strategy, style guides, and UI/UX development to drive efficiency and consistency into our user experience.
- Develop new business model to help improve sales revenue from scratch.
- Create key design deliverables such as wireframe, user flow, mockup, and prototype to present and defend design to executive stakeholders.
- Create UI code HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and jQuery for rapid prototyping.
- Collaborate with outside venders and agencies on projects.
- Research and analyze UI/UX trends, competitors, and strategies.
- Evaluate user feedback received from Customer Service and reviews on Web & App.
- Conduct A/B testing to improve UI/UX and increase conversion rate.

235 S San Pedro St. LA, CA 90012



323.558.8902



elishamklee@gmail.com



https://elishamklee.github.io/portfolio/

# SKILLS

Sketch, Photoshop, Illustrator, Zeplin, Marvel, InVision, Principle

HTML(5), CSS(3), JavaScript, jQuery

#### EDUCATION

BS, Mathematics Major SCH University, Korea

UI/UX Design & Flash ActionScript Certificate Yonsei University, Korea

Prototype & Web Design GN Academy, Korea

# ACHIEVEMENTS

H.I.P.P.O means that HAPPINIESS, INNOVATION, PEOPLE, PASSION, OWNERSHIP. H.I.P.P.O winners have positive energy encourages teammates, stop new challenges, respect others, attempt to think & find it for all of people, and have ownership for successful projects.

#### EXPERIENCE

## CallFire - Sr. UI/Visual Designer

Santa Monica, CA | 04.2013 ~ 07.2014

- Created new design guides based on competitor analysis, new trend research, and company's new marketing strategy.
- Gathered business requirements, define concepts, and redesign campaign materials to meet company's goal.
- Recreated "Ex Texting", co-brand of CallFire, BI & Website (Responsive Design) for branding new identity.
- Directly worked with key members such as Project Manager, UX Director, Marketing Director, and Developers.

#### IOZ Global - Self-employed

Long Beach, CA | 11.2010 ~ 02.2013

Operated and built E-Commerce (K-beauty & Ginseng) with Magento Platform. Gained experience in business strategy, management, SEO, Google Analytics, and finance.

#### SG Interactive – Lead UI/Visual Designer

Irvine, CA | 06.2008 ~ 09.2010

- Lead UI/Web designs for each game to create campaign pages and banners.
- Produced style guides and interactive pages with HTML and CSS
- Designed wireframes, mockups and clickable prototypes for developers.
- Created new email templates for each game to enhance user traffic.

# Hanjin USA – Ecommerce Assistant Manager

Carson, CA | 06.2007 ~ 06.2008

- Created fully interactive and clickable HTML prototypes that were used for stakeholders' presentation.
- Designed marketing assets for newspapers, magazines, shipping envelopes, and brochures.
- Planed, developed, and designed Ecommerce from scratch in collaboration with Korea HQ business, marketing, and development team.

#### URI Global - Sr. UI/Graphic Designer & Account Executive

Culver City, CA | 08.2003 ~ 06.2007

- Worked with major clients such as LG, Hyundai Motor, Pantech, Korean Air, Hanjin USA, and Daewoo.
- Worked with Lead of Graphic Design and Lead of Account Executive to create TV, newspaper, and magazine ads for all clients.
- Recreated UI design of LG Scavenger Hunt micro website according to LG design guides and created prototype with HTML and CSS.
- Created Hyundai Motor, LG online campaign pages and banners with Flash ActionScript
- Communicated with Hanjin USA to develop media strategy and collaborate with outside vender.